http://www.chicken.ca/privacy-policy?locale=en_US

Privacy Policy
I. General
This Privacy Statement outlines the information Chicken Farmers of Canada may collect and how we may use that information. This Privacy Statement applies only to Chicken Farmers of Canada websites that are intended for use by residents of Canada.
II. Personally-Identifiable Information
Chicken Farmers of Canada will only collect personally identifiable information about you (such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) if you provide it to us voluntarily. You can choose not to provide us with such information although this may sometimes affect your ability to participate in certain promotions, including offers of products samples or information or the sending of messages through some of our websites or interactive advertisements.
III. Use of Personally-Identifiable Information
Chicken Farmers of Canada may collect and use your personally identifiable information to help us better understand your needs and how we may improve the products and services that we offer you and to contact you. Your information may be shared with agents or contractors of Chicken Farmers of Canada in connection with services that these individuals or entities perform for Chicken Farmers of Canada. Otherwise, Chicken Farmers of Canada will not disclose your personally identifiable information to others without your consent. The information and promotions in Chicken Farmers of Canada’s websites are directed at residents of Canada and are valid only in Canada unless otherwise indicated on the website. We may sometimes request that you verify you live in Canada so we can be assured that the response or information we provide to you is appropriate for your country of residence. There are circumstances where the use of personally identifiable information may be justified or permitted, or where Chicken Farmers of Canada is obliged to disclose such information, including where Chicken Farmers of Canada is required by law, order or requirement of a court, administrative agency or other government tribunal; to protect the rights, privacy safety or property of others; or where the information is public.
Chicken Farmers of Canada endeavours to ensure that any personally identifiable information provided to us is kept accurate, current and complete for the purposes for which the information is used. Chicken Farmers of Canada keeps such information only as long as it is required and we destroy, delete or convert such information into an anonymous form when it is no longer required.
IV. Security
Chicken Farmers of Canada is committed to keeping secure the data you provide us and will take reasonable precautions to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse or alteration. Agents or contractors of Chicken Farmers of Canada who have access to your personally identifiable information in connection with providing services for Chicken Farmers of Canada are required to keep the information confidential and are not permitted to use such information for any other purpose.
V. Children
If you are under the age of majority in your province or territory of residence, please be sure to ask your parents or other responsible adult for permission before providing any personally identifiable information to us.
VI. Non-personally Identifiable Information Collected Automatically
We may collect information about you that is not personally-identifiable such as the type of Internet browser or computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site. In addition, when you view one of our websites, we may store some information on your computer in the form of a "cookie" or similar file. Cookies allow us to tailor a website or promotion to better match your interests or preferences. Most Internet browsers enable you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. Chicken Farmers of Canada does not collect personally identifiable information automatically, but we may tie information collected automatically to your previously submitted personally identifiable information.
VII. Contact Information
Please contact us at cfc@chicken.ca (addressed in the subject line to our "Chief Privacy Officer") if you have any questions about this Privacy Statement or any personally identifiable information we may have concerning you, or if you would like us to delete any personally identifiable information we may have concerning you.
AMENDMENTS
Chicken Farmers of Canada reserves the right to revise this Privacy Statement at any time subject to applicable law.
Stay Updated
Sign up for our newsletter today!
Alert!
Close
OK
Modal Title!
Close
Error!
